<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>

<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<channel>

<title>SRC - Crew Status</title>
<link>http://www.siskiyourappellers.com/current.php</link>
<description>
	The Crew Status Page provides information on the whereabouts of crewmembers
	and the various projects that we're currently working on.
</description>

<atom:link href="http://www.siskiyourappellers.com/rss.php" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
<lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Feb 2016 23:31:10 -0700</lastBuildDate>
<language>en-us</language>

<title>[Jan 6th] The perm vacancies are now posted on USA...</title>
<link>http://www.siskiyourappellers.com/current.php</link>
<guid>http://www.siskiyourappellers.com/current.php?id=1452098129</guid>
<pubDate>Wed, 06 Jan 2016 09:35:29 -0700</pubDate>
<description>The perm vacancies are now posted on USAJobs with a closing date of January 15th at midnight. Good luck. 

 

16-FIRE-213730G-DBS Government Wide 

 

https://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/425728100 

 

16-FIRE-213730DP-DBS Demo 

 

https://www.usajobs.gov/GetJob/ViewDetails/425728300</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>[Jan 4th] **Hiring Update v2.0** 

 

Permanent GS...</title>
<link>http://www.siskiyourappellers.com/current.php</link>
<guid>http://www.siskiyourappellers.com/current.php?id=1451934285</guid>
<pubDate>Mon, 04 Jan 2016 12:04:45 -0700</pubDate>
<description>**Hiring Update v2.0** 

 

Permanent GS-4/5 Senior Firefighters: 

 

We are currently looking to fill two Senior Firefighters on our crew with target start time to be in the Spring of 2016. We anticipate the vacancy announcements will be posted on USAJobs on or around the 6th of January with a referral list being requested after we complete a 10 day outreach being posted on the Outreach Database. 

If you have an interest in these highly competitive positions, contact the base ASAP to get your name known and schedule a visit.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>[Dec 18th] **HIRING UPDATE** 

 

Current Vacancies...</title>
<link>http://www.siskiyourappellers.com/current.php</link>
<guid>http://www.siskiyourappellers.com/current.php?id=1450465670</guid>
<pubDate>Fri, 18 Dec 2015 12:07:50 -0700</pubDate>
<description>**HIRING UPDATE** 

 

Current Vacancies: 

 

Temporary Seasonal 1039: 

 

The seasonal hiring process for the 2016 fire season has begun with the vacancy announcements for both the GS-4 and GS-5 positions closing on the 7th of December. Now that all the applications are in, we are coordinating within the region in preparation of the regional hiring session to be held in the Eugene, OR area in mid to late February with selections being made in early March. As of now, all dates are approximate so sty flexible. 

 

Since this will be a regional hiring effort, be specific on where you want to work and contact those programs early and often to ensure your best chance. 

 

Permanent GS-4/5 Senior Firefighter: 

 

We are currently outreaching for two Senior Firefighters on our crew with an intent to fill in the Spring of 2016. The outreach announcement will remain posted on the Outreach Database for 14 days after a specific 7 day outreach is completed for the forest. We anticipate the vacancy will be posted on USAJobs on the 21st of December with a referral list being requested on January 5th and hiring of both positions to begin directly after. 

If you have an interest in these highly competitive positions, contact the base ASAP to get your name known and schedule a visit.</description>
</item>

</channel>
</rss>
